And finally, James Comey was arraigned today regarding federal charges of lying to Congress.
You know, just for fun, they should give him this many days.
Yeah.
So apparently Democrats have a new plan to win back young men.
And it's not inventing a time machine to undo the last eight years where dudes wore
moomoo's and a dead guy was elected president.
The party is testing everything from beer ads to left wing influencers.
In other words, they're trying to rebrand a bad product instead of putting out a good one.
They're even trying something called gym outreach.
Yeah, gym outreach, which, by the way, was my stage name when I made those films to pay my way through community college.
Those were the days.
Democrat operatives are paying left leaning fitness influencers to create online content.
Think about that.
They're paying guys to pretend that they're masculine liberals.
And here I thought that was what Hollywood was for.
But the same guys who called physical fitness white supremacy now pretend that they like the bench press.
Finally, a transition that doesn't make you cut anything off except the car.